人人影視
YYeTs.com
■
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
好了  諾蘭來了  我想捉弄他一下
Okay. Nolan's here. I want to screw with him.
應和我一下
Just go with me.
翻譯： 重案組李Sir  青椒  Hannah小頌頌
大家好
Hey, guys!
嗨  諾蘭  今天星期幾
Hey, uh, Nolan, what day is it?
翻譯： 憤怒團  MicroG  安sim
星期二
It's Tuesday.
不  是星期四
No, it's Thursday.
你睡了三天了
You've been asleep for three days.
時間軸： 魔人jo
是啊  我有時會這樣
Yeah, that happens sometimes.
我有個好消息
Anyway, I got some good news!
校對： holyzch
我被隨機抽取得了一臺免費iPhone
I was selected completely at random to get a free iPhone.
總監&后期： 孤帆
-多偶然啊  -天吶  太偶然了
- How random is that? - Oh, my God, so random.
就好像是  艾瑪  好偶然
It's like, hello, random.
我白為這國家打仗了
I fought for this country for nothing.
等下  免費的iPhone  我想要
Oh, wait a minute. A free iPhone? I want one.
抱歉  這是個市場營銷
Sorry, it's some sort of marketing promotion.
你得有這個邀請函才能去那酒店去領
You have to have a special invitation to pick it up at this hotel.
我有  而你沒有
I have one and you don't.
你要咋辦
What are you gonna do about it?
拿回來唄
Take it back.
我不太會欺負人
I'm not a good bully.
我是那種在背后說壞話
I'm more of a talk-behind-your-back-
破壞你名聲的那種人
and ruin-your-reputation kind of a guy.
我們為什么不復印一下這玩意
What's to stop us from copying this thing
然后去拿免費手機
and getting our own free phones?
道德
Ethics.
是啊  把酒放進汽水瓶里的酒鬼還談道德
Oh, yeah, says the alcoholic who puts booze in his soda can.
這不說明我是酒鬼
That doesn't make me an alcoholic.
我放的是"摩根船長"朗姆酒
I put Captain Morgan in here.
這說明我是
That makes me...
海盜
a pirate.
把腳拿下去  摩根船長
Get your foot off my table, Captain Morgan.
你怎么才來
What took you so long?
抱歉  我一直在說服監獄董事會
Sorry, I've been trying to convince the prison board
重組我的治療小組
to give me back my therapy group.
那里有五個人非常需要我的幫助
I've got five guys in there that really need my help.
但是新上任的典獄長把治療小組取消了
But the new warden just shut us down.
你一定氣死了
Well, you must be really pissed.
是的  但是我一直運用我教你們的
Well, I was. But I've been using the same anger tools
憤怒工具讓自己冷靜下來
that I teach you guys to stay calm,
所以我現在沒事了
so I'm okay now.
有人想要核桃嗎
Anybody want a walnut?
沒有  只有我嗎  好吧
No? Just me? Okay.
所以你很平靜
So, you're in control.
可能核桃不管用
Maybe walnuts won't do it.
椰子呢  有人要嗎
Coconut, anyone?
你和典獄長熟嗎  可以走走后門嗎
Are you close enough with the warden to make a personal appeal?
你們是什么關系
I mean, what's your relationship like?
我們的關系
Our relationship?
你比以前的典獄長友好多了
You know, you are a lot friendlier than the old warden.
我只和那個家伙吃過午餐
I only had lunch with that guy.
你只是想吃午餐嗎
Did you just want to have lunch?
我可能有點越界了
I may have jumped the gun here.
不不  你沒有
No, no, no, no. You're perfect.
我從來沒想到一個典獄長可以這么
I just never expected a warden to be so incredibly
性感還有"水陸兩棲"
sexual and amphibious.
你是想說"左右逢源"吧
You mean "Ambidextrous."
不  水陸兩棲
No, amphibious.
你剛才在浴缸里簡直太厲害了
The thing you did in the bathtub was crazy.
我還以為你要溺水了
I thought you were gonna drown for a second.
是啊  我挺厲害的
Yeah, I can be pretty crazy.
我覺得  你要是把剛才的一半錄下來
All I know is, if you put half the stuff you just did on video,
你就發財了
you'd be a rich woman.
其實沒有你想象的那么多錢
Yeah, well, it doesn't pay as well as you think.
是啊  等等  你說什么
Yeah-- whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Excuse me?
這是個秘密
This is between you and me.
我上大學的時候
But, when I was in college,
我和一個閨蜜自制了一個色情視頻
a girlfriend and I made a homemade porn
賺點假期的花費
to make money for spring break.
那也太棒了
Well, that's awesome.
大多數的孩子都是在快餐店打工
Most kids just get a summer job at Quiznos.
我們的關系相當專業
Our relationship was totally professional.
但是她想要競選檢察總長
But now she wants to run for state attorney general
她覺得為重犯提供心理治療
and she thinks that therapy for felons
讓她顯得對犯罪很手軟
makes her look soft on crime.
但我很難受  我不想去告訴
Anyway, I feel awful. I'm not looking forward
這些囚犯他們的小組解散了
to telling theses prisoners that their group is gone.
你一直對女人有一套  查理
I don't know. You're pretty good with women, Charlie.
可能你把她弄上床  就能讓她改變主意了
Maybe if you get her into bed she'll change her mind.
我說的上床  是指  跟她睡覺
And by bed, I mean, you know, sex.
我有很強烈的預感  應該行不通
Yeah, I have a real strong feeling that's not gonna work.
憤怒管理
第二季第七十集
各位今天感覺如何
Hey, guys. How's everybody doing today?
我很好
I'm good, es?
我沒有問題
I got no problem.
你覺得有問題嗎
You got a problem with that?
如果是的話  那我們就有問題了
'Cause if you do, we got problem.
你怎么這個調調
Why are you talking like that?
我聽街坊傳言說
Uh, word on the street is,
進了監獄  必須得挑一個黑幫
when you come to prison, you have to pick a gang.
我不太喜歡雅利安紋身幫
I'm not much for Aryan tattoos,
所以
so, uh...
打算加入拉丁之王
I'm pledging the Latin Kings.
拉丁之王
The Latin Kings?
兄弟  你這么白
Dude, you're so white,
拉丁之王會直接把你拆了吃掉的
the Latin Kings will chop you up and snort you.
不會的  我告訴你
Well, that's not true. I'll have you know
我是波多黎哥保姆養大的
I grew up with a Puerto Rican nanny.
我知道他們的行為習慣
I know how those people act,
思考方式和說話語氣
how they think, how they talk.
是嗎
Oh, really?
他們怎么說話
And how do those people talk?
就是這樣
Like that.
可以把r的音卷得厲害點
I'd consider rolling your Rs more.
我把你的腦袋砍了當球踢  好嗎
I'm going to r-r-roll your head down the stairs, es?
這次的發音非常完美
See, that was perfect.
我覺得現在應該轉移下話題
It's probably a good time to change the subject.
我有壞消息要宣布
Guys, I got some very upsetting news.
典獄長決定取消這個小組診療活動
The warden has decided to shut down this group.
所以今天大概是最后一次
So this is probably our last session together.
-不  查理  她怎么能這樣  -我才剛來這里
- No, Charlie! She can't do that! - But I just got here.
操啊  查理
Damn, Charlie!
這是我有生以來最失望的事
This is my biggest disappointment since
除了我媽媽在法庭上告發我那事之外
my mother turned state's evidence against me.
我知道你很生氣  恩內斯托
I know you're upset, Ernesto,
不過你已經進步了很多
but you've made a lot of progress here
我很為你自豪
and I couldn't be more proud.
也為我自豪吧  查理  我也進步了
Be proud of me, Charlie. I made progress, too.
我以前可鬧騰了  要求很多  你快為我自豪
I used to be so dramatic and needy. Be proud of me!
-你也很不錯  -這不夠
- You've done well, too. - Oh, that's not enough!
你做得極其好
You've done magnificently well.
極其呢
Ooh. Magnificent.
作為一名心理咨詢師  我很同情你
As a psychologist, I have a lot of sympathy
失去了這個小組  查爾斯
for the fact that you're losing this group, Charles.
-謝謝你  -不過介于你在法庭上揭我的短
- Well, thank you. - But since testified against me in court
還把我送進了這么個鳥不拉屎的破地方
and got me thrown into this Pepto-Bismol-colored hell hole...
所以我很開心
I'm really enjoying this.
我有預感  你的墨西哥兄弟會
And I have a feeling that your Mexican fraternity brothers
也會跟你玩得很開心
are going to enjoy you, too.
祝你好運
Good luck.
為什么典獄長要這樣  查理
Why is the warden doing this to us, Charlie?
她想去競選州檢察總長
She wants to run for state attorney general
她是政治家  他們都是騙子
and she's a politician. They're all liars.
我不知道她能這樣騙多久
I don't know how far she thinks she's gonna get anyway.
她可是拍過A片
I mean, she was in a porn.
她也許覺得取消這個小組
I guess she figures shutting down the group
能夠顯得她雷厲風行  從而得到更多投票
is gonna make her look tough on crime and she'll get more votes.
等等  慢點說  慢點說  前面那句
Uh, back up. Back up, back up, back up, back up.
慢點
Back up!
查理  你剛剛是說典獄長拍過A片嗎
Charlie, did you just say the warden did a porn?
你怎么知道
How do you know?
她告訴我她在很久以前拍過一本
Okay, she told me that she made one a long time ago.
我不是故意說出來的  不過管他呢
I didn't mean to say that, but what the hell,
反正也沒什么大不了
I got nothing to lose now anyway.
查理  我收到了短信
Charlie, I just got a text.
典獄長要見你
The warden wants to see you.
我去  那婊子耳朵真靈
Damn, that bitch has good hearing.
告訴她  我這就去
Tell her I'll be right there.
查理灰常勇敢
Charlie is in aqua caliente.
是非常
It's agua.
我他媽用刀子砍死你
I'm gonna cut you so bad.
請不要這樣
Please don't.
-你想見我嗎  -請坐
- You wanted to see me? - Yes, please sit down.
我不想坐下
Maybe I don't want to sit down.
那你就站著吧
Fine. Stand there.
我又想坐下了
I think I'll have a seat.
我知道你很生氣  感覺我背叛了你
Look, I know you're feeling angry and betrayed,
所以我才叫你來這里
which is why I called you in here.
因為你想看看生氣和被背叛是什么樣子嗎
Because you wanted to see what angry and betrayed looks like?
不  因為我準備把集體治療還給你
No, because I want to give you your group back.
這樣啊  那我讓你看看什么叫驚訝吧
Well, then let me show you what surprised looks like.
真的嗎
Really?!
只要你不把那晚我和你說的
As long as you never repeat my little porn story
黃片的事說出去
that slipped out the other night.
當然可以
Yeah. Sure.
那是什么意思
What's that expression?
意思是"伙計  我說那做毛線"
That's what, "Duh, why would I ever do that?" looks like.
你不知道我有多輕松
You have no idea what a relief that is.
有些人會生氣  會報復
Some people would get angry and vindictive
來搞垮別人
and try to screw the other person.
我對自己的標準可是相當高的
Well, I do hold myself to a very high standard.
如果沒事了  我去告訴他們這個好消息
Now, if you'll excuse me, I should tell my group the good news.
還有點別的事
And some other stuff.
是的  我要在15分鐘之內
Yes, I'd like to call and emergency session
進行一個緊急集體治療
with my group in 15 minutes.
好的  謝謝
All right, thanks.
聽著  我有些好奇
Hey, listen, I'm just curious,
你最近在獄中有沒有聽到什么八卦傳聞
have you heard any gossip about anybody here at the prison lately?
我  他們說我什么
Me? What are they saying about me?
不是后來植入的  我的小腿就那樣
No, those are not implants. They're my real calves!
把他們叫下來
Just get my group down.
我的小謠言傳開啦
My fun little rumor took off.
是你說的
That was you?
那么你欠我個人情
Then you owe me a favor.
你介意我和大家說你拍過黃片嗎
Do you mind if I tell everybody in the prison that you did a porn?
黃片  你什么意思
A porn? Why would you say that?
聽著  典獄長把集體治療還給了我
Look, the warden gave me back my group
我把她拍過黃片的事說了出去
and I let it slip that she did a porn.
所以現在我得告訴大家  其實是你拍的
So now I've got to tell everybody I was really talking about you.
想都別想
Don't even think about it.
別擔心  這事挺簡單的  也很雅致
Well, don't worry. It'll be something simple, tasteful.
比如  你和幾個男的在泳池里嘿咻
Like, you doing a couple of guys by a pool.
那一點都不雅致
That is not tasteful.
那泳池的確不錯
It's a really nice pool.
還有噴泉呢
It's got a waterfall.
你太惡心人了
You are repulsive.
你不許和別人說我拍過黃片
And you are not allowed to tell anybody I did that.
再說
Besides,
如果我真的拍成人電影
if I were gonna do an adult film,
背景應該是意大利的文藝復興時期
it would be in Renaissance Italy
我是米開朗基羅的助手
and I would be assistant to Michelangelo,
他剛剛和教皇大吵了一架
who just got in a big fight with the Pope--
恭喜你  你成功把黃片演沒勁了
Congratulations. You just made porn dull.
好吧  我去和大伙兒直說
All right, I'm just gonna be straight with the guys
讓他們別說出去
and ask them not to talk.
他們也不想失去集體治療的機會
They don't want to lose the group, either.
我還是不相信典獄長拍過黃片
I still can't believe the warden would do something like that.
我們都犯過錯誤
Hey, we all make mistakes.
她的錯誤是把這事告訴了我
Hers was telling me she did a porn.
艾德  你來這里我有點驚訝
I'm a little surprised you're here, Ed.
你根本不喜歡智能手機
You don't even like smartphones.
反正不要錢啊  就算是霍亂我也排隊
It's free. I'd stand in line for cholera if it's free.
你這人真虛偽
You're such a hypocrite.
你總是雞婆說人們如何
You're always bitching about how people
過于依賴手機  但事實不是這樣的
are too dependent on their smartphones, but that's not true.
聽著  我剛剛用我的...
Here, look. I just used mine for--
天啊  不見了
Oh, my God! It's gone!
我手機不見了  死了死了
My phone's gone! I'm dead! I'm dead!
活不了了  天啊  在這呢
I'm dead! Oh, my God! Oh, here it is.
伙計們  咱們沒戲了
Hey, guys, we're screwed.
前面的人說只發了50份邀請函
Someone up there just said they only sent out 50 invitations
那意味著  只有50部免費手機
and that means there are only 50 free phones.
-那又怎樣  -我數了隊伍里的人
- So what? - Well, I counted everyone in line
諾蘭是第50個
and Nolan is number 50.
我贏了
I made it!
諾蘭  如果你是第50個
Nolan, if you're 50,
我可以插你前面嗎
can I cut in front of you
那樣我就是第49個  你是第50個
so that I can be 49 and then you can be 50?
沒問題
Sure.
我還在50人里
I'm still in it!
那么  蕾西
So, Lacey,
我和艾德可以站你前面嗎  我們是47和48
could Ed and I move in front of you and be number 47 and 48?
好的  等等
Fine. Wait a second!
可以  沒事的
Yeah, that still works.
太棒了
This is great!
我們都有手機拿了
We're all gonna get phones.
等等
Hey, wait a second.
你是第50個
You're number 50.
意味著只有你才能拿到手機
That means you're the only one that gets a phone.
天哪  你真是太對了  我覺得糟透了
Oh, my God, you're right. I feel terrible.
我一拿到免費手機就給你發道歉短信啊
As soon as I get my free phone I'll text you all an apology.
帕特里克 把諾蘭的位子還給他  你個混蛋
Patrick, give Nolan his spot back. You're being a jerk.
-謝謝  蕾西  -不客氣
- Thank you, Lacey. - You're welcome.
諾蘭  我對你這么好
Uh, Nolan, for being so nice to you,
-我能再排到第49嗎  -當然
- can I be 49 again? - Of course!
謝謝你們這么快就過來了
Thanks for coming in on such short notice, guys.
非常感謝  查理
I appreciate that, Charlie.
大多數人不肯承認我們也很忙
Most people don't acknowledge our busy schedules.
我只是想讓大家知道
I just want to let everyone know
我們的治療小組重新開張了
that our therapy group is back in business.
太好了  太好了
Ooh! That is wonderful! That is wonderful!
還有一件事
There's just one more thing.
我今天好像說過
I may have said something today
你們誰都不能告訴的事情
that you guys can't tell anybody.
是哪件事  查理
What was it, Charlie?
就是典獄長拍過色情小電影這事
That thing about the warden doing a porn.
對了  我完全忘了
Oh, that's right! I completely forgot.
典獄長  她拍過色情小電影
The warden, she did a porn!
謝謝你提醒我們啊
Thanks for reminding us.
我就知道我想告訴別人什么事情的
I knew there was something I wanted to tell people.
千萬別  我可是認真的
No, guys, guys, guys. Seriously.
如果你告訴任何人  典獄長肯定會知道
If you tell anyone, the warden will know it
是我說出去的  然后她又會解散小組了
was me and she'll take our group away again.
別擔心  查理  我們會替你保密的
Don't worry, Charlie. Your secret's safe with us.
沒錯  在監獄里第三壞的就是告密
Yeah, the third worst thing in prison you can be is a snitch,
排在猥褻兒童犯和警察殺手之后
after child molester and cop killer.
是"殺手"
Killer.
好  謝謝你們了  周四見
Well, thanks, guys. See you Thursday.
查理
Uh, you know, Charlie,
雖然你毀了我的生活
even though you've ruined my life,
但我想讓你知道我也不會告密的
I want you to know your secret is safe with me, too.
-你要我做什么  -沒什么
- What's the catch? - There is no catch.
你要不幫我干件事
You just have to do something
要不我就全都告訴典獄長
for me or I'll tell the warden everything.
這就是"要求"  這就是"要求"的定義啊
That's a catch. That's the definition of a catch.
我正要敲詐你呢  查理
I'm about to blackmail you, Charlie.
你真的想玩文字游戲嗎
Do you really want to quibble?
-你想要什么  -三樣簡單的東西
- What do you want? - Three simple things.
一包烏茲別克斯坦進口野杏仁
A bag of wild almonds from Uzbekistan,
一個做成溫斯頓·丘吉爾模樣的蠟燭
a candle in the shape of Winston Churchill,
還有6.5盎司[200毫升左右]的
and six and one half ounces of
正宗日本烏賊墨
authentic Japanese squid ink.
如果只有8盎司裝[約240毫升]也行
If it only comes in eight ounces, get that.
我不想顯得不可理喻
I don't want to be unreasonable.
你想做什么  在丘吉爾融化的臉
What are you gonna do, eat almonds and write a haiku
所發出的亮光下吃杏仁寫俳句嗎
by the light of Winston Churchill's melting face?
也許吧
Maybe.
你只是想故意找事為難我吧
You're just picking impossible to find crap to screw with me.
哪有啊  如果我真想為難你
Oh, please! If I really wanted to screw with you,
我就會讓你在24小時內搞定
I'd make you do this in 24 hours.
等等  現在你只有24小時了
Oh, wait! You have 24 hours.
下午好  女士
Good afternoon, ma'am.
這是領免費手機的隊
Is this the line for the free phone?
還是選美國小姐的秀場啊
Or the Miss America pageant?
讓我猜猜
Let me guess,
你是阿拉斯加小姐吧
you're Miss Alaska.
我要問你芳齡幾何
I'll ask ya how old you are,
但我知道我會聽到你說30歲
but I know I'll hear 30.
額滴神吶
Jesus Christ.
你介意我和你站在一隊嗎
You mind if I stand here in line with you?
給我滾出去
Get the hell out of here!
很高興見到你
Nice to meet you.
你至少70了吧
You're 70 if you're a day.
搞定了嗎  他們要開始發手機了
Any luck? They're about to start handing out the phones.
沒有  沒人想讓位
No, nobody wants to give up their spot.
我們不可能騙這些人讓我們排到前面去的
We'll never move up in this line by tricking these people.
我們得唬他們  我喊失火了然后你們一起尖叫
We have to panic them. I'll yell fire and then you all scream.
這蠢爆了  沒人會信你們的
That's stupid. Nobody's gonna believe you.
我會縱火然后你們再尖叫
I'll start a fire and then you guys scream.
這高明多了  這是我的打火機
That's much better. Here's my lighter.
真無恥  你們曉得你們做壞事
Shame on you. You know when you do bad things,
壞事也會纏上你們吧
bad things happen to you.
-你是諾蘭·約翰遜嗎  -是的
- Are you Nolan Johnson? - Yes, I am.
好了  50個人了
Okay, that's 50!
所有人聽著  這是個騙局
Everyone, this is a sting!
所有拿到傳單的人都因未交違停罰款被逮捕
Anyone with a flier, you're under arrest for unpaid parking tickets.
這免費手機最好值這個價
Boy, this free phone better be worth it.
快走
Let's go.
-您好  您需要什么  -你好
- Oh, yes. Can I help you? - Yeah, hi.
我是打電話問溫斯頓·丘吉爾蠟燭的那個人
I'm the guy that called about the Winston Churchill candle.
哦  是的  就在那
Oh, yes. It's right here.
哦  太好了  多少錢
Oh, great. How much is it?
哦  這不賣
Oh, it's not for sale.
但是我打電話的時候  你說你有一個
But when I called, you told me that you had one.
我是有一個  在這
I do have one. It's right here.
但是你從來沒問這個賣不賣
But you never asked if it was for sale.
我怎么會大電話問蠟燭但是又不買呢
Why would I call about the candle if I didn't want to buy it?
人們有時感覺寂寞
People get lonely.
他們打電話因為他們想要跟別人說話
They call because they want to talk to other people.
我不知道  我也不批評
I don't know. I don't judge.
這個皮帕·米德爾頓的烤箱手套怎么樣
How about this Pippa Middleton oven mitt?
-我需要那個蠟燭  -你還沒看看它呢
- I need that candle! - You haven't even looked at it.
她在彎腰呢
She's bending over.
好吧
Okay.
我買了
I'll take it.
但是你不懂
But you don't understand,
我有了堅果  也有了墨水
I've got the nuts. I've got the ink.
就差溫斯頓·丘吉爾了
All I need now is Winston Churchill!
你要的東西真是喪心病狂
That's some drug-induced scavenger hunt you're on.
這是一個無價的傳家寶
This is a priceless family heirloom
我父親在諾曼底海灘上雕刻了這個
My father carved this on the beach at Normandy.
這上面有個標簽寫著"中國制造"
It's got a sticker on it that says "Made in China."
是嗎
It does?
也許是他在中國的沙灘上刻得吧
Oh, well, maybe he carved it on a beach in China.
不管如何  都是在戰爭時期
Either way, there was a war on.
聽著  你父親沒有做這個
Look, your father didn't make this.
-你要多少錢  -500美元
- How much you want for it? - 500.
-我給你100 -真的嗎  我賣了
- I'll give you 100. - Seriously? I'll take it.
你為什么不一開始就要價呢
Why didn't you just ask for that in the first place?
人們有時感覺寂寞  想要跟別人說話
People get lonely. They want to talk to other people.
那么  告訴我  你來自哪里
So, tell me, where are you from?
不好意思  哥們  我要走了
Sorry, dude, I gotta go.
再見
Good-bye.
諾蘭  我們因為你被抓感到很抱歉
So, Nolan, we felt really bad about you getting arrested,
所以我們給你弄了個東西
so we got you something.
哦  上帝  一個新手機
Oh, my God! A new phone?
太感謝了
Aw, thank you so much!
你們還刻了字啊
You even had it engraved?
幫我  我叫長富
"Help! My name is Chang Foo.
我14歲  我被逼在全天黑暗
I'm 14 years old. I'm forced to make phones
沒有廁所的工廠里做手機
all day in dark factory with no toilet."
上帝  哥們們
Oh, my God, you guys.
這太完美了
That is so beautiful.
謝謝  這是我寫的
Thanks. I wrote that.
不好意思  我遲到了  朋友們
Sorry I'm late, guys.
真是個瘋狂的早晨
It's been a crazy morning.
你又把鑰匙丟在在一堆脫衣舞女下面了
You lose your car keys under a pile of strippers again?
不是一堆脫衣舞女
It's not a pile of strippers.
正確的術語應該是一群脫衣舞女
The correct term is a gaggle of strippers.
但是那還不是瘋狂的部分
But that's not the crazy part.
我在城里轉了一圈了
I've been running all over town
買烏茲別克野生杏仁
picking up Uzbeki wild almonds,
日本烏賊墨水
Japanese squid ink,
和一個雕成溫斯頓·丘吉爾的蠟燭
and a candle shaped like Winston Churchill.
我以為是一隊脫衣舞女
I thought it was a pride of strippers.
不是  是一隊妓女  一群脫衣舞女
No, it's a pride of hookers, a gaggle of strippers,
和一窩熟婦
and a swarm of MILFs.
查理  你要那些東西做什么
What do you need all that stuff for, Charlie?
你要越獄嘛
Are you escaping from prison?
什么
What?
你為什么這么說
Why would you say that?
你可以用野生杏仁里的氰化物
Well, you could use the cyanide from the wild almonds
來制造假昏迷混進監獄醫院
to enter a coma-like trance to get into the prison hospital.
蠟燭的蠟可以用來塑造一個鑰匙
The wax from the candle is to mold a key to get out of your room.
然后你只需要跳著華爾茲
Then all you have to do is waltz
穿著用床單縫紉的
out the front door in your prison chaplain uniform
和烏賊墨染成的牧師服
which you sewed from your bed sheets
就可以離開前門了
and dyed black with the squid ink.
哦  上帝啊
Oh, my God!
他就是要這么干
That's exactly what he's doing.
你是怎么想到的
How did you put that together?
想到什么
Put what together?
我要從他那里把這些東西要回來
I gotta get that stuff back from him.
好了  你們呆在這里
All right, you guys stay here
讓諾蘭給你們解釋一下世界經濟形勢
and have Nolan explain the world economy to you.
我極大程度的低估了那個人
We have vastly underestimated that man.
看  他是在偽裝昏迷
See? He's in a fake coma.
他已經離越獄成功不遠了
He's halfway through his plan to escape.
你是怎么推斷出
How did you put it together
他會吃杏仁造成氰化物中毒
that he was gonna use the almonds for cyanide
然后用溫斯頓·丘吉爾蠟燭塑把鑰匙的
and a Winston Churchill candle to mold a key?
喬丹  你真是又傻又天真
Oh, Jordan, you're so naive.
是人都能想到吧
How could you not put that together?
好了  蘭迪  起來  戲唱完了
All right, Randy, wake up. It's over.
回你的牢房去  蘭迪  起來
You're going back to your cell. Randy, wake up!
游戲結束了  你個狗娘養的
Game's over, you son of a bitch!
快起來  蘭迪
Wake up! Randy!
你到底在干嘛
What the hell are you doing?!
-病人已經昏迷了  -他才沒有
- That man's in a coma. - No, he's not.
他用丘吉爾做了把鑰匙
He's hiding a key
就藏在他屁股后面
he made out of Winston Churchill in his ass.
護工
Orderly!
他隨時都會醒  瞧好了
He's gonna wake up any second. Watch.
住手
Stop it!
這人就因為幾顆杏仁差點被獄友捅死
You're shaking a man who was almost stabbed to death
你還使勁晃他
by his cellmate over some almonds.
他才不是  這是個騙局
No he wasn't. It's a trick.
別跟他一般見識
You'll have to excuse him.
我們覺得這是他小腿種植體的不良反應
We think he's having an adverse reaction to his calf implants.
不  不  我說的是真的
No, no, no. It's true.
如果他被捅了  應該渾身都是刺傷
If he'd been stabbed, he'd be covered in stab wounds.
的確都是刺傷
That's a lot of stab wounds.
知道了  謝謝  好消息
Got it. Thank you. Good news.
他們要把蘭迪醫生轉到
Just found out they're transferring Dr. Randy
其他監獄的醫院去
to a hospital in a different prison.
順便提一句  我是對的
And by the way, I was right.
在他的內褲里的確找到了蠟制的鑰匙
They found a wax key in his underwear.
顯然丘吉爾花了一整晚才逃出生天
Apparently it took Churchill all night to tunnel out.
我外公曾經說過--
Well, it's like my grandpappy used to say--
說真的  就這你還能想出至理名言來
Really?! You have a countryism for this?
我能
Yes, I do.
如果負鼠偷了你的巧克力蛋糕
If a possum has your brownies,
別管他是睡著了還是死了
don't ask if he's sleeping or dead,
負鼠的特征是擅長裝死
拿上蛋糕走人就對了
just get your brownies back and walk away.
你外公真是喝多了
Your grandpappy drank a lot.
那倒是
Oh, yeah.
他在哪兒都能看到負鼠和巧克力蛋糕
He saw possums and brownies everywhere.
查理
Charlie!
你沒告訴過我恩內斯托的中名是西維亞
You never told me Ernesto's middle name is Sylvia.
這是私人檔案  克羅
These are private files, Cleo.
你不該看
You're not supposed to be looking at 'em.
不過這事我也不知道  太詭異了
But I didn't know that either. That's really weird.
打擾一下  谷德森
Excuse me, Goodson.
-能私下聊兩句嗎  -當然
- Can I talk to you in private for a minute? - Sure.
我只是想說你病人蘭迪醫生的事我很遺憾
I just wanted to say, I'm sorry about your patient, Dr. Randy.
謝謝  我們都很震驚
Thank you. It was a shock to all of us.
但我也聽說你不斷地搖他還扇他
Although I did hear you shook and slapped him repeatedly.
對  我是那么干了
I did. Yes, I did.
我只是太悲慟了
I was just so grief-stricken.
順便告訴你  "悲慟"這個詞
Not sure if you know, but "Grief-stricken"
是從德語"悲痛"來的
comes from the German, "Greifstracken,"
意思是悲痛大發了
which means to grieve violently.
這周對我倆來說都不好過
Well, look, it's been a bit of a rough week for both of us.
但我想我們能從頭來一遍
But I thought maybe we could start over.
你有沒有興趣--
Would you be interested in--
德語里是怎么說來著--
what's the German word for it--
"重赴巫山"
"Resumen-der-boinken"?
那真是棒呆了
Ja. Das ist gut.
不好意思打擾一下
Sorry to interrupt.
醫務室的人剛剛送來了這個
Someone from the infirmary just dropped this off.
我猜蘭迪醫生醒了過來
I guess Dr. Randy woke up from his coma,
寫張字條  然后又昏過去了
wrote this note, and then slipped back into unconsciousness.
"典獄長沒出生"  什么意思
"The warden wasn't born." What does that mean?
"典獄長沒出生"  說不通啊
"The warden wasn't born." That doesn't make any sense.
不是不是  寫的是"典獄長拍三級"
No, no, no, no! That says "The warden was in porn."
他失血過多了  把P寫倒了
He lost a lot of blood. His P's upside-down.
不對  寫的就是"典獄長沒出生"
No, it says "The warden wasn't born."
克羅  繼續歸檔去
Cleo, go back to filing.
-你個混蛋  -不  不  不  不
- You bastard! - No, no, no, no!
寫的是"喬丹"
It says "Jordan."
"喬丹拍三級"
"Jordan was in porn."
對吧  喬丹
Right, Jordan?
告訴她你跟神父搞上的事
Tell her about the time you had sex with the Pope.